Reese Pearsall

Bozeman, Montana • (406)672-3268 • reesepearsallcs@gmail.com • https://reesep.github.io

Summary

Hard working and motivated student working towards degree in computer science with experience working in academia and government. Interested in the field of cybersecurity, cybercrime, and cyberlaw. Knowledgeable in numerous programming languages. Planning on pursuing a career in undergraduate education after graduate school.

Education

Montana State University Bozeman- (Expected Graduation Summer 2020)

- Expected Degree: Bachelor of Science Computer Science Sociology (minor)
- Current GPA: 3.7

Skills

- Proficient in Python and Java
- Basic knowledge and understanding of Go, C, C#, C++, HTML and CSS
- Microsoft Office Suite, NetBeans, Microsoft Visual Studios, Eclipse, Git, Mercurial
- Experience leading and working in a team-oriented setting
- Strong communication, teaching, and public speaking skills

Work Experience

United States Air Force

May 2019 – August 2019

Software Engineering Intern – Hill Air Force, Utah

- Worked together with a development team to create an updated and modernized calibration software that tests the working condition of a (unclassified) mobile ground radar system.
- Gained experience working in a DevOps and Agile environment.
- Work included software testing and implantation of new software features using a variety of technical resources and libraries.
- Obtained a security clearance to gain the ability to work on various Air Force technologies.

TechLink February 2019 - Present

<u>Software Engineering Intern – Bozeman, Montana</u>

- Member of the TechLink Software Engineering and Analysis Laboratory (TSEAL).
- Develop automated testing solutions for Department of Defense enterprise software.
- Gain experience using a wide variety of testing tools and libraries, including Selenium, basic Visual Studios testing tools, SpecFlow, and creating step definitions with Gherkin/C#.

Montana State University - Gianforte School of Computing

<u>Undergraduate Teaching Assistant – Bozeman, Montana</u>

August 2018 - Present

CSCI 127 – Joy and Beauty of Data (Fall 2018, Spring 2019, Fall 2019)

CSCI 491 – Programming in Go (study abroad course in Berlin, Germany – Summer 2020)

- Assist undergraduate students with understanding topics taught in lecture through weekly help sessions and one-on-one support.
- Responsible for grading the work of 30+ undergraduate students and holding a weekly lab section.
- Provide operational and additional grading support for lead instructor.